http://www.goldeneyeforever.com/privacypolicy.php

GoldenEye Multiplayer on Nintendo 64 / N64
GoldenEyeForever.com Privacy Policy
We respect your right to privacy. None of the information we collect is passed on to other parties, except when required as part of the business services we provide for you, or as required under Canadian law.
Data Collection
We collect no data about you save for that captured by a cookie to provide us with anonymous information about site navigation.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of text information created by websites and stored on your computer. We only use cookies to provide us with anonymous information about site navigation. No other information is stored in cookies, and cookies are not used for any other purpose. You should also be aware that whilst the above paragraph describes our use of cookies, some advertisers on this site may also collect data using cookies. The use of cookies and/or web beacons to collect data is used in the ad serving process. We do not have access to this data. Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their previous visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Protection
We will not retain any details that you provide, except for your email address if you contact us and this will never be disclosed to third parties.
Links
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy statements/policies of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.
Click image to visit our
Perfect Dark Content
:: Quick Links To Our GoldenEye Pages and Content ::
:: Multiplayer Levels :: Gameshark Codes ::
Cheats :: GE Rogue Agent :: Weapons ::
Emulator :: Videos :: Forum :: Contact :: Privacy Policy :: Page Top::
::How To Play GoldenEye Online :: How To Play New GoldenEye N64 Multiplayer Levels ::
:: Quick Links To Our Perfect Dark Pages and Content ::
: How To Play Perfect Dark Online :: Perfect Dark Cheats :: How To Win At Perfect Dark
::
